脉搏有力
He's got a good pulse.
保持头部稳定 把他翻过来
Maintain headabcstabilizationand flip him over.
听我指令 预备 翻
My count, guys. Ready. Go.
先生 我们是医护人员
Sir, we're paramedics.
邮差见到你在痉挛
The mailman saw you having a seizure.
我们只好破门而入了
We had to break downyour door.
你知道自己的名字吗?
Do you know what your name is?
听我指令 1 2 3起
On my count. One, two, three. Up.
我们把你送去医院
We're taking youto the hospital.
不 我不能--abc不 不 我不能...
No, I can't--abcno. No, I can't...
伙计 伙计 我们想帮你
Hey, buddy. Buddy, we're trying to help.
先生!
Sir!
别进来!
Stay out of my house!
你刚刚痉挛过
You just had a seizure.
有可能是中风 大脑可能出血了
You could have a stroke.abcA bleed in your brain.
走开!
Leave me alone!
男 35岁--剧烈头痛abc过去2天有3次痉挛发作
35-year-old male-- crushing headacheabcand three seizures in the last two days.
那么就是出血 凝块 肿瘤abc代谢问题或者感染了
so it's a bleed, clot, tumor,abcmetabolic, or infection.
-把他塞进CT仪里abc-不能
- Stick him in a ct.abc- Can'T.
他头太大塞不进?
I'm assuming he has a giant head.
患有严重的惧旷症
Severe agoraphobe.
整个世界都使他害怕
The world scares the hell out of him.
我们只能用能带过去的仪器检查他
So we can only test him withabcwhatever we can take to him.
好玩
Fun.
惧旷是个症状吗?
Agoraphobia a symptom?
只是中枪后才这样
Only of being shot.
他和女友7年前遭遇歹徒abc就是从那时起的
He and his girlfriend were muggedabcseven years ago. That's when it started.
人中枪后憎恨人类很正常
Anybody can hate humanityabcafter getting shot.
中枪前就恨上了 只有伟人才做得到
Takes a big man to hate it beforehand.
他连急诊室都到不了abc你是怎么接到案子的
How'd you get this case ifabche didn't come to the er?
去年他患感冒时我跟他隔门对话过
I talked to him through hisabcdoor when he had flu last year.
我现在负责社区扩展服务项目了
I run the community outreach pgram now.
瞧 完美合理的解释
See? Perfectly reasonable explanation.
她明显不是想费尽心思归队abc抢你们的饭碗或怎样
She's definitely not here trying to work her wayabcback on the team and steal your job or anything.
我是从合法角度问的问题
It's a legitimate question.
他答应见我们
He agreed to meet with us.
但即使我可以进他的房子abc他的大脑是个黑匣子
But even if I can get inside hisabchouse, his brain is a black box.
我们等会再接着聊
We can pick this up in a minute.
这是什么?
what's this?
外卖菜单
Take-out menus.
不过我希望你想个好点的回答abc方便大家等下问到
But I'm hoping you'll come up with a betterabcanswer when everyone asks what we're talking about.
-昨晚--abc-不说这个
- Last night--abc- forget it.
我知道有些尴尬 但是我们得谈谈
I know this is awkward,abcbut we need to talk.
我们进化出来尴尬这种感觉是有原因的
There's a reason that we'veabcevolved a feeling of awkwardness.
这样就知道不该谈某些事
It tells us not to talk about things.
我当时因为领养不成而失落
I was emotional because ofabcthe adoption falling through.
而你的人性一面展现了一会儿
And you actually let yourabchuman side show for a moment.
这是我们接吻的原因
That is why we kissed.
我只是想谢谢你没...趁机占便宜
I just want to say thank youabcfor not... taking advantage.
不客气
You're welcome.
啥时候不想接吻了 就找我
Any time you want to stopabckissing, I'm there for you.
便携仪器无法辨别出血点或肿瘤abc也无法看到血管炎
Portable equipment can't distinguish aabcbleed or a tumor. Can't see vasculitis.
Cuddy想干嘛?
What did cuddy want?
我们昨晚好像做得很爽abc她现在死缠着我不放了
I kinda hit that last night,abcso now she's all on my jock.
对服过迷奸药的人来说 她气色不错
She looks pretty goodabcfor someone on roofies.
唯一可用的就是超声波扫描仪abc和便携式X光扫描仪
The only equipment we have isabca sonogram and a portable x-ray.
橄榄石 辉石 闪石 不懂哪个?
What part of olivine, pyroxene,abcand amphibole don't you understand?
辉石
pyroxene.
辉指的是"光辉"...
Pyro means "fire"...
他们都是指引矿石
they're indicator minerals.
你是看不到钻石的abc所以只能从指引矿石着手
You can't see diamonds so youabclook for the indicator minerals.
假设钻石指的是肿瘤或出血点或别的什么
I assume the diamond is theabctumor or bleed or whatever it is.
我们可以触发痉挛
we provoke a seizure.
集中在异常区域的增长电活性就是指引
The indicator is the increased electricalabcactivity focused around the abnormality.
做个脑电图 看集中在哪abc就知道问题是什么了
We do an eeg, see the focus, see where theabcproblem is, whh tells us what the problem is.
老福满和小凯美仑
The formster and the camster.
玩转母校~
Kickin' it old school.
幸亏她没打算抢你们饭碗
Thank god she's notabctrying to steal your job.
干活吧 查查房子有没有毒素
Go do it. And searchabcthe home for toxins.
我答应对话 没说让你进来
I agreed to talk, not let you in.
你可能病得厉害
You could be very sick.
我们得进去看看
We need access.
我还没准备好
I'm just not ready.
为啥有两扇门?
Why does hhave two locked doors?
他肯定是用这间房作为气锁
He must use this room as an airlock.
送货进来 扔垃圾出去abc他就不必出门了
Deliveries in. Garbage out.abcHe never has to go outside.
准备好了告诉我们
Just tell us when you are.
我们哪都不去
We're not going away.
真的?
Seriously?
你想让她承认只要他忽视我们一阵abc我们就会走了?
You want her to admit that all he has to do isabcignore us for a few minutes and we'll take off?
他中过枪
He was shot.
女友被杀了
Girlfriend killed.
他很有可能患有创伤后应激障碍
He probably has postabctraumatic stress disorder.
他对什么人什么事都不信任
He doesn't believe in a justabcuniverse. He doesn't trust anyone.
要对他说老实话
Give him some hostY.
我不该暗示我们会一直等你
I shouldn't have impliedabcwe'd wait forever.
事实上有整个医院的病人在等着
We've got a wholeabchospital full of patients.
我们只会给你几分钟
We can give you a few minutes.
要是最后你还是不让我们进来 就得走了
But eventually, if you don't letabcus in, we're gonna have to leave.
只准让一个人进来
just one person comes in.
不 我们还得检查整间房子有没有毒素
No. We've got to searchabcthe whole house for toxins.
要不我在一间房间给你检查abc我同事可以检查其他地方?
How about I examine you in one roomabcand my colleagues will do the search?
我要激发痉挛
I'm gonna tryto provoke a seizure.
需要你直视前方 好吗?
I need youto look straight ahead, okay?
你还好吗?
You all right?
我只是很久没跟别人呆在一间房里了
Yeah. Uh, I just, um, I haven't beenabcin a room with anyone for a while.
- 可以给我点时间吗?abc- 行
- Um, can you just give me a second?abc- Sure.
你是去年我隔着门说过话的人 对吗?
You're the, uh, uh, person I talkedabcto through the door last year, right?
是的
Yeah.
你人很好 也很聪明
You were, uh, youabcwere nice... and smart.
我以为是个年纪大点的人
Kind of made me expect someone older.
我也没那么年轻
I'm not that young.
枪击事件肯定把你吓坏了
Must've been scary being shot.
别这样 好吗?
Don't do that. Okay?
你不了解我
You d--youabcdon't know me.
这里有我需要的一切
I've got everything I want here.
我帮人写说明书赚不少钱
I-I-I make a lot ofabcmoney writing tech manuals.
东西可以送货上门 我也做运动
I get stuff delivered. I work out.
通过网络可以了解外面一切
I see anything I want over the web.
我在这很开心
Um, I'm--I'mabchappy here.
你看上去不像很开心
Yodon't seemvery happy.
我现在不开心而已
Well, right now I'm not.
走开
Go away.
你昨晚跟Cuddy聊过了?
Did you speak to cuddy last night?
她很好
She's fine.
忘记一个用错感情的小孩abc不用花很长时间的
Why would it take anyone more than aabcfew hours to get over misplacing a baby?
你跟她谈过了?
You spoke to her?
我们做得很爽
Kinda hit that.
所以她缠着我不放了
So she's all on my jock.
什-什么?
Wha--what?
别人听见都认为我在开玩笑
Everyone else thought I was kidding.
你们做了? 亲热 上床还是--
You hit?Like makingabcout or full-on sex or--
画张"垒"的示意图 我再细细道来
got a chart laid out with all theabcbases. I'll take you through it.
你打算怎么办?
Wh--what areabcyou gonna do?
我能怎么办?
What can I do?
我打算这辈子都不理她了
I'm going to ignoreabcherfor the rest of my life.
蚊子包害我睡不着
This mosquito bite kept me awake.
我才不管蚊子包
Don't careabout the bug bite.
她是你老板
She's your boss.
这样我就有两个不理她的理由了
So now I have two reasonsto ignore her.
只是接个吻而已
It was just a kiss.
接吻是有原因的
There's a reason.
原因就是她胸罩里面那两大团
Yes. Those large things in her bra.
你躲着我就证明这事对你意味着什么
You were hiding it from meabcmeans it meant somethingto you.
是啊 我邪恶地将此事隐藏在abc"做得爽"这句话里了
Yeah, I fiendishly concealed itabcwithin the phrase"I hit that."
别抓了 要出血了
Stop scratching. You'll draw blood.
终于说了句有用的了
Finally you saidsomething useful.
要是我抓破皮了 毒素会扩散
If I actually break the skin,abcit'll let the poison out.
要是你跟Cuddy约会 这样--
If you... datedabccuddy...there would--
抱歉 你不在的话 信号会好点
sorry. I get betterabcreception when you're not here.
查到什么?
What do you got?
他家很干净
his place is totally clean.
没有动物 没藏有毒品或酒精abc油漆里不含铅
No animals. No hidden drugs orabcalcohol. No lead in the paint.
既然你们没呼吸急促
and since you're not breathing hard,
我想你们也没把Cameron抛起以庆祝abc就是说没有激发出痉挛
I assume you're not holding cameron aloftabcin triumph. Which means no seizures.
说到呼吸急促abcCameron 你跟Chase订婚了没?
Speakingof breathing hard,abccameron, you engaged to chase yet?
抱歉 刚才我们应该先说清楚
sorry, we should have clarified.
我们打来是关于病人abc不是要说Cameron的爱情生活的
We're callingabout the patient,abcnot . Cameron'slove life.
我们没有订婚
We aren't engaged.
直接回答他的问题这样效率高些
Moves things alongmuch fasterabcto just give himthe answers.
- 要触发痉挛只有在--abc- 都6年了还没?
- Seizures can alsobe inducedabcthrough-- - after six years?
1年半
A year and a half.
- 剥夺睡眠时或abc- 剥夺睡眠花的时间太长了
- Through sleep deprivation or-- -abcsleep deprivationwould take too long.
你们同居了?
You living together?
常一起过夜
We spend most nightstogether.
有很多药物可以使痉挛容易被触发
There's a bunch of drugs thatabccan lower a seizurethreshold.
药物副作用会使诊断不明朗
And cloud theabcdiagnosis with side effects.
他家还是你家?
His place or yours?
一般在他家
His usually.
有趣
Interesting.
不管我怎么答你都会说有趣的
You would've saidinterestingabcno matterwhat the answer.
不管你怎么答都很有趣啊
And no matter what the answer,abcit would've been interesting.
还没订婚 承诺问题
No engagement. Commitment issues.
在他家过夜 控制问题
His place, control issues.
还不清楚是谁的问题 但仍有趣
Not sure whose,but interesting.
是啊 这样效率更高了
Yeah, moves much fasterthis way.
病人第一次痉挛时在哪?
Where was the patientwhenabche had his first seizure?
在他的门口拿邮件时
In his entry hallway getting his mail.
接近外界吓着他了 脉搏上升
Getting close to theabcoutdoors spooked him, raised his bp.
利用他的恐惧 带他去外面
Use that fear. Bring him outside.
他连消防队员都打
He punched out a fireman.
我们是医生 又不是保安
We're doctors, not bouncers.
那好 就把外界带到他身边吧
Okay. So bring the outside to him.
地板是实木的
Floor is genuine wood.
他们来干嘛?
Why are they here?
他们偶然听见我在急诊室abc说有半价出售的房子
They overheard me announce the half priceabcbank foreclosure in the er waiting room.
他们在哪?
Where's everybody?
Cameron跟病人呆在一起
Cameron'swith the patient.
其他人回家了
Uh, everybody else went home.
因为他们不必呆在这
Because they don't need to be here.
你也不必
Neither do you.
但你却在
And yet you are.
这边走
This way.
装饰线脚是原有的吗?
Molding's original?
原有?
Original?
在房子建起之前就有了
They were here before the house.
关在房子里的人也是原有的
The shut-in's also original.
来 别害羞
Come on. Don't be shy.
House 让他们出去
House, get themout of here.
说就容易
easy for you to say.
你又不打算认真投资赚钱
You're not gonna be makingsomeabcserious capital gains.
这样太残忍了
This is cruel.
那放着不帮他断症是啥 无私的?
And leaving him undiagnosedabcis what, altruistic?
成了 他痉挛了 仪器显示什么?
Procedure worked. He'sabcseizing. What do you see?
θ波正常
Normal theta.
δ波正常 这不是痉挛
Normal delta. This isn't a seizure.
总是点什么
It's something.
Nozick先生 你还好么?
Mr. Nozick,are you okay?
肚子疼死了
Stomach's killing me.
看吧 肯定有问题
See? It's something.
局部肠梗阻
partial small bowel obstruction.
梗阻可以解释疼痛
Blockage expinsthe pain.
再加上痉挛发作 怎么解释?
What explainsthe blockage plus seizures?
心房纤颤 导致栓塞
Atrial fibrillation throwing emboli.
克罗恩病导致的脓肿
Crohn's causing an abscess.
原因有一大把呢
Could bea million things.
根本没法下定论 除非去医院给他的abc头部做核磁共振或者探测手术
There's no way to know unless we get him inabcfor an mri on his head or exploratory surgeryso
然后才能给肠做活检 但他不让
we can biopsy his bowels,abcwhich he won't let us do.
从前不让
Wouldn't.
疼痛可以改变一切
Pain changes things.
House
House.
他说过让你在外面待着
He told you to stay out of here.
等他不想忍受剧痛了abc再把我赶走也不迟
He can chase me out once he'sabcdone doubling up in agony.
不管你有啥问题 它引起了一种abc叫"结肠Fos"的并发症 Fo就是充满
Whatever yr big problem is, it's caused aabccomplication we call "colon fos." "Fo," full of.
有女士在场 s代表粪便
Since we're in mixedabccompany,"s" is stool.
因为无法排出 疼痛会越来越严重
Nothing's coming out so theabcpain'sgonna get worse and worse.
我们要给你用拾便器
We need to sticka pooper scooper in you.
还要看一眼你的肠子
We also need to takeabca lookat your bowel.
我的意愿已经说得很清楚了
I made my wishes clear.
如果有仙女疯了 你的愿望就能成真
And if the crazy fairy wereabchere, she could grant them.
我没疯
I'm not insane.
我-我一出门就觉得疼
I-I feel painwhen I go outside.
所以--逃避疼痛合情合理
So it--it's rationaltoabcavoid that pain.
但你在屋里也疼
Except now you're feeling pain inside.
没那么糟 差太多了
Not as bad. Nowhere near.
我们可以为肠梗阻用药
We can give him drugsfor the blockage.
要是不起作用呢?
And if it doesn't work?
梗阻会撕裂你的肠道abc把污物喷得你身体里到处都是
That blockage will ruptureyour intestines,abcspew sewage throughout your body.
不管你怕什么 你难道不怕死亡么?
Whatever you're scared ofout there,abcaren't you more scared of death?
很明显你无法与人共处
You obviouslycan't stand people.
但我比你更糟
But for me, it's worse. All right?
我宁可死掉也不出去
I'd rather die inabchere than live out there.
如果你对乱糟糟的头发abc和恼人口音没意见的话
If you don't mind floppyabchair and an annoying accent,
我认识个医生abc可以为你在家里动手术
I know a surgeonwho willabcoperate in your home.
谢谢
Thank you.
冒着感染的危险 Chase才不会...
With the risk of infection,abcchase won't actually--
他才不肯在个疯子家里动手术呢
he's not gonna do surgeryinabcsome crazy dude's house.
你刚刚还说...
You justabcsaid--
我刚才是说 Chase会在他家里麻醉
what I said was that chaseabcwould put him under at the house,
我们带他回医院 开刀 动手术
we'd take himto the hospital,abcopen him up,do our thing,
再把他带回房间做术后照护abc他就不会发觉我们晃了他
then slip him backinto his room for the post-opabcwithout him ever finding outthat we tricked him.
我是想用隐喻来着
Some of that was implied.
- 这是违背伦理的abc- 他都被麻倒了
- It's unethical.abc- He'll be asleep.
即使被麻醉了 他仍有决定权
He gets to makehis ownabccalls even if he's asleeP.
你干嘛跟他一拨?
Why are you sidingwith him?
哦 对啊 你就是喜欢残破的人abc因为你丈夫死了
Oh, yeah, you're that girlwho likesabcbroken people because her husband died.
而Chase又不那么残破--
And since chaseabcisn'tall that broken--
说到这 干嘛不给腿部肌肉梗死的家伙abc动个手术?
hey, why don't we operateon hisabcinfarcted leg while we're at it?
谁管他同不同意呢
Who cares if he said no.
我是冒着生命危险abc不想变成个瘸子
I was risking my lifetoabcavoid becoming a cripple.
他却这样逃避阳光和新鲜空气
He's doing it toabcavoidsunlight and fresh air.
我们绝不能出半点岔子
We've got to make it look good.
我很让人讨厌
I know I'm a pain in the ass.
转身离开很容易 但是...
I know it would have beenabceasy just to walk away, but...
你是个好人
you're a good person.
从10开始倒数
Count down from 10.
10 9 8...
10, 9, 8...
走吧!
let's go!
感觉怎么样?
How you doin'?
- 好些了abc- 那就好
- Better.abc- Great.
其他也都好?
Everything else good?
呃 我与House那惊鸿一吻的事也都还好
Uh, everything involvingabcme kissing house is good.
哦 天呐 被你八卦到了
Oh, god, you dragged itout of me.
你太厉害了
You're a genius.
这没什么大不了的
It's no big deal.
我当时很伤感
I was feeling vulnerable.
他只是个朋友
He's a friend.
给我一时的依靠
And I leaned on him.
有意思 我也曾依靠过我的朋友
It's funny. I've leanedabcon friendsin the past.
但从没靠得那么近abc把舌头都靠到他们嘴里去了
Never leaned so far myabctonguefell into their mouths.
我没动过House的心思 从来没有过
I don't think of housethatabcway. I never have.
为什么没有?
Why not?
你很清楚结果会怎样
You know exactlyhow it would go.
一开始很刺激
It'd start off exciting.
完全沉迷于新奇感 互不相让abc禁忌中做乐
We'd get caught up in the novelty and theabchostility and the forbiddenness.
接着意识到打情骂俏变成了势不两立
And then we'd realize that theabcflirty hostility is just hostility
而他抑郁的气质也不那么刺激了abc反而让人觉得沮丧
and his inabilityto open up is noabclonger exciting,it's just frustrating.
然后 双方无可避免地abc开始争吵 相互指责
And--and then it'sthe inevitableabcblowup and the recriminations
两个月都不跟对方说话
and we don't talkfor two months.
是哦
Yeah.
还真是证明了你从来没对House动过心思
Well, it certainly proves you'veabcnever thoughtabout house that way.
我明白你的意思了
I get your point.
以后我说话会多加小心
I will be more carefulwithabcmy tongue in the future.
我不是这个意思
That's not my point.
也许玩玩新鲜 闹闹别扭 破破规矩abc也不一定会遗憾收场
Maybe novelty and hostilityandabcforbidden-ness doesn't have to end bad.
得走了
Gotta go.
你什么时候下班?
What time you done?
我们可以去我家附近abc新开的寿司店尝尝鲜
We could trythat new sushiabcplace next to my house.
今晚去我那怎么样?
Why don't we stayat my house tonight?
咱们总是住我家的啊
We always stayat mine.
我就是这意思 以前是轮流住的abc怎么变了呢?
That's what I mean. We--weabcused to split it. What happened?
不知道 上班近点呗
I don't know. Closer to work.
近5分钟而已
By five minutes.
而且我家看着可不像是abc醉酒的橄榄球员装修的
Anmy house doesn't looklike it wasabcdecorated by a drunk rugby player.
我们晚些再讨论吧 我还没...
Well, we can discussabcit.I hadn't really--
干嘛还非得讨论?abc你就不能过来住一晚么?
why does it haveto be aabcdiscussion? Can't you juststay over?
你们该知道 那么多手术器械被签出的时候abc他们会通知我
You do know they page me when thatabcmuch surgical equipment is signed out.
- 他没有同意abc- 他同意手术了 难道还会上诉手术地?
He didn't consent. He consentedto theabcsurgery. You think he's gonnasue over where?
他根本不知情 他醒来的时候就在家了abc他不会知道发生了什么
He won't even know where. He'll wake up in hisabchouse. He won't know a thing about what happened.
除非他在肮脏的小房子里发生了abc术后感染 然后发觉我们晃了他
Until he catchesa post-surgical infection inabchis dirty apartmentand finds out we tricked him
最终怪到医院头上
and winds up owningthe hospital.
你干嘛不跟她争论?
Why aren't you arguingwith her?
因为她说得对
Because she's right.
我才不在乎他在哪感染abc但不能感染
I don't care where he gets theabcpost-op, just that he gets it.
把他留在医院
Keep him here.
House 你还好么?
House. You okay?
好得很 我们不用详谈
Yes. We don't need to talk.
你的手
Your hand.
真诡异
That's weird.
我一般到复活节才会有圣痕
I usually don't get theabcstigmata until easter.
告诉Chase医生abc病人已准备好进行手术了
Please tell dr. Chase theabcpatient's ready for him now.
Stewart 醒醒 我是Cameron医生
Stewart, wake up. It's dr. Cameron.
如果能听见我说话 你就眨眨眼
If you can hear me, blink.
出于安全考虑 我们把你带到了医院
We were concernedfor your safetyabcso we brought youto the hospital.
不 没事的
No, it's okay.
为--为什么?
Why--why?
- 没事的 没事的abc- 为什么...
- No, it's okay.abc- Why...
我只是想让你知道
I just wantedto keep you informed.
我不想你在术后恢复的时候受到惊吓
I didn't want youto have a bad shockabcwhile you were recoveringfrom surgery.
我得离开这
Gotta get outta of here.
没事的 Stewart 冷静abc别激动 Stewart
It's okay, stewart. Calmabcdown. Calm down. Stewart.
Stewart 我要给你注射镇静剂
Stewart,I'm gonna sedate you.
让你镇定下来
I'm gonnasedate you.
不要!
No!
冷静点!
Calm down.
我需要帮助! 该死! 来个人帮忙啊!
I need some helpin here!abcDamn it! Somebody get in here!
你做了什么?
What did you do?
做得真不错啊
well done.
病人叫了律师 威胁说要告我们
Your patientcalled hisabclawyer, threatened to sue us.
他现在回家去了 完全没有确诊
He's now heading homeabccompletely undiagnosed.
他很快就会回来的
He'll sooneon his way back.
他有病 他撑不住的 会失去知觉
He's sick. He'll crash.abcHe'll lose consciousness.
到时候我就派个急救车把他接回来
I'll declare anabcemergency,bring him back in.
你已经无权这么做了
Not anymore you won'T.
现在他的医疗保健由律师代理
His lawyer now holdshisabchealth care proxy.
下次急诊时 敬爱的abcLarry Ruseckas先生说了算
The next time we havean emergency, larryabcruseckas, esquire,will be calling the shots.
我的选择是正确的
I made the right call.
如果他在大手术之后暴怒abc结果更加不堪设想
If he'd flipped outafter majorabcsurgery, it would've been worse.
做上司的好处就是我无需争论
The benefit of being bossisabcthat I don't have to argue.
这个病例你们都别管了
You're all off the case.
你跟Cuddy之间怎么了?
What's going on betweenyou and cuddy?
爱之深 恨之切
Bad lovin' gone bad.
说认真的 你干嘛不跟她吵?
Seriously. Why didn'tyou argue with her?
她让我们丢了病例
She just threw usoff the case.
因为无视她要容易很多
Because ignoring heris a lot easier.
说服病人让我们回他屋里
Convince the patienttoabclet us back in again.
试试能否用乳果糖abc治好他的小肠梗阻
See if you can clearhisabcblockage with lactulose.
如果还没确诊 他就这样死了abc可一点也不好玩
If this thing kills himbefore we canabcdiagnose, it won't be fun anymore.
好吧
Okay.
你还要继续做下去?
You gonna keepworking on this?
是啊 这病例是我拿来的
Yeah. I brought inthe case.
没病例了 病人走了abc不让你们管了 还犯什么傻啊
There is no case. He's gone. You'veabcbeen tossed. This is totally nuts.
他病得很重 我们不知道--
He's incrediblyabcsick.We don't know--
得了 别说那病人了 你是怎么回事?
forget about the patient.abcWhat is going on with you?
我们离开House的团队就是abc为了避免持续不断地抓狂
This is why we lefthouse'team to avoidabcthis constant floodof pure craziness.
那是我离开House的原因
That's why I left house.
你是被炒掉的
You got fired.
我很抱歉 我知道我让你失望了
I'm sorry. I know I l you down.
但你知道我还让谁失望了?abc所有那些对我很重要的人
But you know who elseI let down, prettyabcmuch everyonewho's important to me.
我的上司 我以前的上司 还有我男朋友
My boss, my old boss, my boyfriend.
我这么做都是为了你
I did that for you.
我不会再让你失望了
I'm not gonnalet you down again.
这简直就是"红色白痴勋章"abc(引:南北战争背景小说"红色勇气勋章")
It's like the red badge of idiocy.
如果南部邦联里有蚊子的话 那我们现在abc都得说南部口音 Foreman会很便宜
If the confederacy had mosquitoes, we'd all haveabcsouthern accentsand I'd be paying foreman less.
她让你丢了病例
She kicked youoff the case.
不正视问题的结果就是这样
This is what happensabcwhen you don't address it.
她举止诡异 事情一反常态
She acts weird,things get different.
你该知道 差异终究会导致分歧
You understand thatabcdifferentimplies difference.
她以前就让我丢过无数个案例
She's tossed mea million times before.
没有 她刁难你后
No, she always chastises you.
你都会找我发牢骚
And you'd always comeabcrunningto mto complain.
所以 你也一反常态
So you're actingdifferent too.
你是害怕了
You're scared.
你害怕触及感情
You are scaredto get involved.
那有什么好怕的?
How is that "scared"?
这合情合理
It's rational.
心智成熟的同事之间不应当千丝万缕
Emotionally mature people whoabcwork together should not de.
注定会分道扬镳
Guaranteed breakup.
注定以难堪收场
Guaranteed ugliness.
每段感情 最后不是分手就是死亡
Any relationshipthat doesn'tabcend in a breakup ends in death.
走到尽头 万物皆逝
Everything falls apartin the end.
这可是你的世界观啊
That's your worldview.
总被你抹杀的推论abc就是应该抓住每一个幸福的可能
The corollary,which you keep forgetting, isabcthat you have to grab any chance for happiness.
你干嘛对这件事这么上心?
Why does this matterso much to you?
我和Cuddy好着呢
Cuddy and I are fine.
唯一大惊小怪的人就是你
The only persongettingabcworked up here is you.
我不想你用"好着呢"来敷衍
I don't want youto be fine.
我想要你快乐 我觉得abc如果你跟她约会的话--
I want you to be happy.Iabcthink if you dated her---
你对"替身"这词熟悉不?
are you familiar withabcthe adverb "vicariously"?
如果我想跟她约会--
If I wanted toabcask her out--
你是约过她 去年 感觉如何?
you did ask her out.Lastabcyear. Whatever happened there?
我不清楚 我不感兴趣
I don't know. I wasn't interested.
错 你当然感兴趣
Wrong. You were interested.
但是Amber先一步把你拴牢了
But amber grabbedyour genitals first.
但是现在你单身啦 所以你很悲戚
But now you're single, andabcthat makes you miserable
而你又觉得梅开二度为时尚早
because you think it's tooabcsoonfor another relationship.
所以你想让我跟你一样悲戚
So you're gonnamake me miserable.
拜托 去找个女友 过另一段生活abc或别的什么
Please, get a girlfriend,orabca life, or something.
权当为了我
For me.
好转还是恶化了?
Better or worse?
恶化了 药物不起作用
worse. Drugs aren't working.
我想应该像原计划那样abc在他家做手术
I think we should do the surgeryabcin his house like we planned.
你当时没听清我的话么abc这只是骗他上当的桥段
Well, then one of uswasn't paying attention becauseabcI thought that surgerything was just a trick.
我们把房间准备好 挂上隔菌帘
We prepared the room.abcWe hung the drapes.
这比战场上的移动手术室干净十倍
It's probably ten timesas sterile as anyabcmobile operating theater you'd find in a battlefield.
我们还得找个"风流医生"abc(引电视剧)
We still need trapper john.
Chase不愿趟这趟浑水
Chase doesn't wantanywhereabcnear this surgery.
也许你可以劝劝他
Maybe you could talk to him.
我听不懂他的口音
I can't understanda word he says.
Taub
Taub.
待会儿有事吗?
Doing anything later?
出血了
Blood in the field.
不要挡住我视线
Not where I'm looking.
我怎么知道你的视线在哪?
How am I supposedto knowabcwhere you're looking?
还用说吗 当然是出血那里
Here's a hint. It's the bloody part.
这家伙身上有个大洞 到处都是血
The whole thing's bloody. It'sabca guy with a hole in his body.
你好像从没干过这个似的 用吸管
It's like you've neverdoneabcthis before. Use the ction.
晓得了
I will.
我的确从没干过这个abc我上的是医学院 不是护士学校
And in fact I'venever done this beforeabcbecause I went to med school,not nurse school.
嘿 想看看你的客户有多少油水吗?
Hey, wanna see if yourabcclient's actually made of money?
切下一片肠
Cutting out last piece of bowel.
缝合
Suture.
粘膜呈粉红色
Mucosa's pink.
绒毛扁平
Flattened villi.
肠道萎缩
Intestinal atrophy.
是惠普尔病abc(肠源性脂肪代谢障碍)
It's whipple's disease.
解释了痉挛和肚子痛
Explains the seizureandabcthe stomach pain.
这儿有点出血
Little bleeder here.
灼烧
Cautery.
嘿 慢着 气体-
Hey,abcwait.The gas--
这种事在手术室时有发生
That always happensduring surgery.
因气体在肠梗阻处积聚
Just the gas build up in the blockage.
没什么好起诉的
Nothing to sue about.
给他处理烧伤
Treat him for the burns.
上抗生素治疗惠普尔病
Put him on antibioticsabcfor the whipple's.
他会好起来的
He'll be fine.
你真好
That's niceof you.
病人怎么样了?
He doing good?
烧伤处理好了 情况也稳定了
Uh, burns are healingabcfine. He's stable otherwise.
好 如果你想的话abc我今晚可以留在你家
Good. So, uh, I could stayatabcyour place tonight if you'd like.
我不行
I can'T.
你不会又在这过夜吧
Well, you're not gonna sleep here again.
你也看到了 没有护士
You might haveabcnoticedthe lack of nurses.
你又不负责这个病例
Because you're not on the case.
你不能老拿这个当借口...
You can't really use thatas an excuse...
- Cameron医生!abc- 你等着
- dr. Cameron!abc- Wait here.
腹痛?
Your stomach?
我的腿麻木了
My legs are numb.
我完全感觉不到
I can't feel them at all.
出现新症状 外周神经病变abc用抗生素后恶化 不是惠普尔病
New symptom. Peripheral neuropathy. Gotabcworse on antibiotics. It's not whipple'S.
- 卟啉病abc- 肝没事
- porphyria.abc- liver's fine.
淀粉样变性病
Amyloidosis.
应该在肠道里就看到了
We would've seen iton the intestines.
我们在肠道里看到了什么?
What did we seeon the intestines?
粘膜呈粉红色 绒毛扁平
Pink mucosa, flattened villi.
不是惠普尔病 那就是乳糜泻
It's not whipple's,abcit's gotta be celiac.
小麦过敏意味着他不能吸收营养
Wheat allergy meanshe'sabcnot absorbing nutrients.
解释了痉挛 肚子痛abc还有现在的神经病变
Explains the seizures,stomach,abcand now the nerves.
要做个血液测试乳糜泻
we should run a blood test for celiac.
不够快 不够精准
Not fast enough. Not accurate enough.
强迫他吃小麦 然后做内窥镜检查abc看小麦进入十二指肠时
Force-feed him wheat then do anabcendoscopy as it hits his duodenum.
是否出现过敏症状
See if there's an allergicreaction.
他的肠子炸开了
His guts just exploded.
强迫进食可能会引发痛楚
It might be a tadabcpainfulto make him eat.
这正中House下怀
That's house's point.
他这么做不是为了诊断
There's nothing diagnostic about it.
而是让病人疼痛不堪abc好逼他离开房间
He's trying to put the patientabcin pain, force him to come in.
这个测试可行
It is a lid test.
做血液测试吧 没有痛楚
So is the blood test,which is painless.
Foreman 电话传出的声音abc此际在你脑海里久久回荡
foreman, listen to that little voice inabcyour head that's comingfrom the telephone.
强迫进食
Force-feed him.
不要
Don'T.
你了解House 你知道我才是对的
You know house. You know I'm right.
两个测试一起做
We'll do both tests.
我不是来当媒人的
I'm not here to play matchmaker.
好吧
Okay.
House其实...
House basically...
他说我对你有意思
well, he accused me ofabcbeing interested in you.
他只是想转移话题
Oh, he's just tryingtoabcchange the subject.
我知道 但我的确...
I know. But I do have...
一直...对你...有感觉
I've always... had...abcsome feelings for you.
你是说 你想和我约会?
Are you sayingyou want to date me?
不 我-这对House不公平abc而且Amber过身不久
No. I-I--it wouldn'tbe fair toabchouse and it's too soonafter amber.
但你觉得你应该说出来
But you thoughtyou should just say it.
是的 我想应该让你知道
Yeah. I thought you should know.
明晚我们一起吃饭吧
Let's have dinner tomorrow night.
好
Okay.
或者直接...上床效果更好
Or maybe it would beabcbetterif we just... had sex.
你说什么?
Pardon me?
干脆在House的办公室前好了
In front of house's office.
不然他看不到就白费工夫了
I mean, I don't want to take any chances.
我猜 你是为了让House吃醋
I assume the point ofabcthisis to make him jealous
好意识到自己想和我发展关系?
and make him realizethat heabcdoes want a relationship with me?
是的
Yes.
你说这行得通吗?
You think it'll work?
你是个白痴
You're an idiot.
相信我
Trust me.
我和House不约会 大家会好过得多
Everybody will be happierabcif house and iaren't dating.
你肯定这是最好的测试方法?
You sure this is the best test?
不 但你限制了我们可用的手段
No. But you've kindof tied our hands.
当食物进入肠道时abc我会透过内窥镜观察
Soon as this hits your intestines,abcI'll look at it through an endoscope.
Stewart 我知道你不想谈这个 但...
Stewart, I know you don'tabcwant to talk about this, but...
人中枪后会患上创伤后应激障碍
people who get shotoften get ptsd.
没什么好羞愧的
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
通过药物和治疗 完全可以治愈
It's very treatablewithabcdrugs and therapy.
这不是PTSD
It's not ptsd.
我中枪时 我女友和我在一起 她死了
My girlfriend was with mewhenabcI got shot and she died.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这正是我想说的abc我也曾失去我爱的人
But that's what I mean.abcI lost someone myself.
我深知这种痛苦
I know it's traumatic.
不 我-我的意思是...
No, what--what--what I'mabctryingto say is that...
我中枪前就是这样了
I was like thisbefore the shooting.
我还是个孩子时
Sie I was a kid.
一切对我来说都很困难
Everything was hard for me.
我-我不怎么出门 一旦出门...
I--I didn't go outthatabcmuch. And--and when I did...
恐惧就会袭来
I had panic attacks.
和肉体上的痛楚无异
Like physical pain.
不 比这还要糟糕abc像是快死了一样
No, it was, like, worse.abcIt was like I was dying.
直至遇到Angela
Then I met angela.
她是我唯一想出门的理由
She was the only reasonabcthat I ever wantedto go out.
但后来她死了...
But then she died. And...
血液测试快做好了
Blood test will be done soon.
我猜 这是一项新的检测技术
I'm guessing that's a new technique.
嘿 还记得Cameron那个主意么?abc"折磨病人迫使他承认自己的问题"
Hey, you remember that idea that cameron had aboutabctrying to torture the patient into admitting himself?
我很笃定这是你的主意
Pretty sureit was your idea.
你想我拖延测试?
You want me to slow down the test?
瓦 今天每个人都变得好聪明
Everyone's got allabcthesegreat ideas today.
病人不肯离开 是因为会带来痛楚abc我们就让他留在房间里更痛苦
So you're thinking patient won't leave because leavingabccauses pain, so we gotta make staying more painful.
这招肯定能行
That actually makes sense.
你只能增加他的痛楚abc但还不足以让他出门
You'll increase his pain, butabcnot enoughto make a difference.
他在注射吗啡
He's on morphine.
他现在有吗啡护航
He's on morphine now.
很快就没这待遇了
Pretty soon he'll beon less-phine.
因为当你去补充药物时abc会把点滴换成生理盐水
'Cause when you restock, you'll actuallyabcbe givingcameron iv bags of saline.
你凭什么认为我会这么干?
And why do you thinkI'll be doing this?
和你答应做手术一个理由
Same reason you didthe surgery.
因为当时是紧急情况
That was becauseit was an emergency.
不
No.
是因为你的婚姻完蛋了
It was because yourabcmarriageis falling apart.
你承认出轨 情势便急转直下
When you confess adultery,abcthings tend to go bad.
当人生像泰坦尼克号触礁沉没abc你划着小艇逃离它的残骸 开创新生
When one part of your life does a titanic,abcyou make a life raft out of whatever's left,
工作对你而言更重要了abc所以你答应做手术
which makes your jobmore significant,abcwhich is why you didthe surgery,
所以你值夜班abc所以你会照我说的干
why you pulled an all-nighter,abcand why you'll do this.
她让我睡在沙发上
She's having me sleepon the couch.
几个晚上而已
Just for a few nights.
我这么干不是为了保住工作
I'm not doing thisto save my job.
而是为了救他的命
I'm doing this to savehis life.
没错 我会这么对大伙说的
Right. That's what we'll telleveryone.
你有没有想过 这种时候abc你想去的其实不是我家?
Have you considered that it's not my placeabcyou really want to be walkinginto right now?
Ric Ocasek的歌声会杀了我 如果我去--abc哦 你说的是Cuddy
Ric ocasek would kill meifabcI-- oh, you mean cuddy.
没错 她是有点神经质
Yeah, she's a little nuts.
但她漂亮 聪明 有趣abc最重要的是 她受得了你
But she's beautiful,smart, funny,abcand most important,she can stand you.
没错 我是来听你介绍Cuddy的讲座
Yeah. I came here toabchaveyou lecture me on cuddy,
而不是为了躲避我家一只abc成天缠绕不休的催命蚊子
not because there'sa killer mosquitoabcchasing me aroundmy apartment.
House 根本没有什么蚊子
House,there is no mosquito.
一切都是因为Cuddy
This is all about cuddy.
原来是她在叮咬我
Ah, she's bugging me.
真有诗意
Poetic.
你看到那蚊子了吗?
Have you seen this bug?
你看到这叮破的口子了吗?
Have you seen this bite?
没有 我只看到一个被你挠破abc并致坏疽感染化脓的伤口
No. What I've seen is a suppurating wound that you'veabcscratched and mutilated into a gangrenous state.
寄生虫妄想症
Delusional parasitosis.
我不是在妄想
I am not imagining things.
House 你是药物依赖者
House, you'rea drug addict.
你一直都在妄想
You're alwaysimagining things.
自从吻了她 你就妄想被叮了
You got bitten the night you kissed her.
每当你想起她 就会越来越痒
Your itching always getsabcworsewhen you think about her.
你得把事情弄明白
You need to address this.
她是我上司
She's my boss.
不 你害怕的不是她的权威
No, you're not afraid of authority.
你害怕的是 她是那个最适合你的人
You're afraid sheabcactuallyis right for you.
你害怕冒险 因为风险太大了
You're afraidto take a chanceabcbecause it's too biga chance.
如果和她合不来abc世上就再没人适合你了
If it doesn't workwith her, thenabcmaybe there'sno one out there.
我不跟你辩论
I am not rationalizing.
我一个人活得好好的
I'm better off alone.
你最近留意她屁股了么?
Also, you seen her assrecently?
不准你留在这里
You're not staying here.
- 噢 拜托abc- 不行 你要么回家
- Oh, come on.abc- No. You can go home.
要么就去Cuddy那儿 摁她门铃
Or you're goingto cuddy's,abcgonna ring her doorbell,
像个正常人那样 把她约出去
and you're gonna ask herout onabca date like regular people do
凌晨3点?
at 3:00 in the morning?
- 正常人什么时候睡觉?abc- 拜拜
- When do regular peopleabcsleep? - Buh-bye.
他痛得想去医院了么?
Is he in enough pain to come in yet?
没有
No.
抗体测试有结果了么?
Antibody tests back?
没结果
Inconclusive.
那你来干什么?
Then why are you here?
我想你了
I missed you.
内窥镜检查呢?
Endoscopy?
没结果
Inconclusive.
那就再做一遍
Well, then do it again.
我知道这很难受abc但我必须再一次检查你的胃
I know it sucks, but I needabcto test your stomach again.
很痛
it's really hurting.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
试着坐起来 张开嘴巴
Try to get youon your backabcand have you open your mouth.
我不...
I can't...
他昏过去了 有反应么?
He's out. Anything?
没有脉搏 心肺复苏
No pulse. Start cpr.
拿电极板 拿来 你打给谁?
Get the paddles. Get theabcpaddles! Who are you calling?
订批萨 你要凤尾鱼的么?
Pizza. You like anchovies?
我打给律师 情况紧急
I'm calling the lawyer.abcGenuine emergency.
- 他会同意送医院abc- 他要不行了
- He'll okay admission.abc- He's dying.
没错
Exactly.
吵醒你了吗
Sorry to wake you.
你那个自闭的客户心脏病发
Your introvert is having a heart attack.
如果不重启他的心脏
If we don't restart his heart...
靠吸氧和心肺复苏术 他能活15分钟
he can survive 15abcminutes on oxygen and cpr.
能在5分钟内送他到医院
We can get himto the hospital in five.
律师同意了 作心肺复苏
Lawyer says yes. Continue cpr.
Holden Green道2123号 病人无脉搏
2123 holden green. Patient with P. E. A.
- 让开abc- 别!
- Clear.abc- Wait!
有脉搏了
I got a pulse.
让救护车别来了
Cancel the ambulance.
他稳定了 可以留在这儿
He's stable enoughto stay here.
恢复窦性节律 但仍心动过缓
his heart's back to sinusabcrhythm, but it's bradycardic.
Taub给他装了临时心脏起搏器
Taub's putting ina temporary pacemaker.
暂时维持他的心率
It'll keep his heartbeating for now.
Cameron 你回来我手下干吧
hey, cameron, how wouldabcyou likeyour old job back?
这样我才能炒了你
I'm asking 'cause it'stheabconly way I can fire you.
抱歉
Sorry.
在急诊室 我们得救活病人abc而不是眼看着他们苦苦挣扎
In er, we like to actually resuscitateabcdying people, not just let them flop around.
可能是淋巴瘤
Could be lymphoma.
应该能在腹部看到
We'd have seen iton the abdomen.
是毒素
It has to be a poison.
有机磷酸酯
Organophosphates.
把他家查了又查
we checked the place over and over.
很干净
It's completely clean.
门口有玫瑰花瓣
There are rose petals in the front entry.
除非他一天吃一束花 不然
Unless he's eating aabcbouquet a day, he couldn't--
- 有多干净?abc- 相当干净
- how clean?abc- Very.
他可能有点儿洁癖
He probably has a little ocd.
你多久擦一次浴缸?
How often do you wash your tub?
隔几天
Every couple days.
漂白剂和氨水?
Bleach and ammonia?
是的
Yeah.
见过小孩在洗澡时玩小兵打仗么?
You know how kids playabctoy soldiers in the bath?
他每周三次用气体重演伊普尔战役
He likes to re-enact the battle ofabcypres three times a week with real gas.
氨水和漂白剂会产生氯气
Ammonia and bleach makes chlorine gas.
高度脂溶
Highly fat soluble.
他在腹痛后体重减轻
He lost weight after the stomach pain.
能解释为什么他的症状持续恶化
Explains why hisabcsymptoms kept getting worse.
静脉注射类固醇和碳酸氢钠
Put him on parenteralabcsteroids and sodium bicarbonate.
即使你是对的 临时起搏器总会失效
even if you're right, that externalabcpacemaker's gonna fail eventually.
我没本事装一个永久的
And I don't have the skillstoabcput in a permanent one.
也许毒素没有彻底毁坏心脏
Well, maybe the poisonabchasn'tcompletely shot his heart.
这样你就不用终身感到内疚了
And you won't haveto feelabcguilty for the rest of your life.
没有显像仪 我怎么在右心室上找准地方?
How am I gonna place the leads in the exactabcspot on the right ventricle without fluoroscopy?
靠压力?
The force?
Taub装了临时的
Taub put in the temporary one.
你们去玩蒙眼给驴装尾巴好啦
You can do that playing pinabcthe tail on the donkey.
永久起搏器要非常精准
Permanent pacemakers need precision.
可以用便携式X射线成像仪
So we can use the portable x-ray.
不是实时的
It's not real time.
超声波扫描仪
Sonogram.
要是超声仪不够精确abc我导致他室颤了怎么办?
And what happens when I put him into v-tachabcbecause the sonogram isn't precise enough?
他要死了
He's dying.
所以我才不想做害死他的人
Exactly why I don'twantabcto be the one to kill him.
谢
Thanks.
我知道我会拒绝的
You knew I'd haveto say no.
但你还是来找我
But you came anyway.
你是想有个借口对我发火
You just wanted aabcreasonto be angry at me.
- 如果我们之间有问题abc- 别绕
- If there's somethingabcwrongbetween us, then-- - forget it.
我们为什么老在我那儿过夜
You know whywe spend nights at my house?
因为在你家过夜时
Because when we spend themat yours...
我察觉到你不想我待在那儿
I could tellyou didn't want me there.
我不想你过来 干嘛还频频喊你来
Why would I keepinviting youabcover if I didn'twant you there?
每天早上你一定会赶我走
You always kicked me outevery morning.
你不让我用抽屉
You never offered me a drawer.
没有空出一个柜子给我
You never cleared outyour closet for me.
我只是个访客
I was just a visitor.
你什么时候有这种感觉的?
How long have you feltlike this?
从一开始
From the start.
我理解你失去过丈夫abc所以很难走出来 但
I know it's hard for youbecauseabcyou lost your husband, but...
我不能永远追寻你
I can't keep chasing youforever.
打你家没人接 你在哪儿?
I just tried your house. Where are you?
在泡吧 好消息还是坏消息?
Clubbing. Good or bad?
坏 生命体征减弱
Bad. Vitals are dropping.
腹部疼痛变得更剧烈
The abdominal painkeeps getting worse.
治疗得太晚了
Means we were tooabclatewith the treatment.
告诉律师可以不用计时了
Tell the lawyerhe's off the clock.
玩完了
We're done.
你要放弃?
You're giving up?
叫Taub
Call taub.
让他带点吗啡
Tell him to pick upsome morphine.
病人没必要受苦了
There's no needfor theabcpatient to be in pain.
他在用吗啡
He's on morphine.
不 他吊生理盐水
No. He's on saline.
我发现你让他吊生理盐水abc就换回吗啡了
I figured you put himon salineabcso I switched him backto morphine.
爱你
I love you.
你到法定做爱年龄 一定要通知我
When you reachabcpuberty,give me--
腹痛 已经用吗啡
his abdominal pain.abcThat was on morphine?
是的
Yes.
有什么导致腹痛不受吗啡抑制?
Is there something that causes abdominalabcpain that doesn't respond to morphine?
我是对的
I was right.
他被下毒了
He is being poisoned.
髋部的密度如何?
What's this density on his hip?
只是骨头
Just bone.
没那么硬骨头
Think less boney.
你认为他是铅中毒?
You think he's got lead poisoning?
解释了便秘 神经系统病 痉挛
Explains the constipation,abcthe nerves, seizes.
摁住他
Hold him down.
你不会有感觉
You're not gonna feela thing...
除非痛到极点
except excruciating pain.
歹徒用的是空尖弹
The mugger used hollow points.
爆炸留下碎片
They explodedand left fragments.
几片碎片藏在你髋骨后abc医生遗漏了没取出
Your doctors missed a coupleabchiding behind your hip bone.
小意思
It's no biggie.
可几年后 铅弹融化abc大事不妙 你开始融化
Except years later, they started to dissolve,abcand then, biggie, you started to dissolve.
我给他用螯合剂
I'll start him on chelation.
陌生环境恐怖症 会不会也是--
The agoraphobia,could it--
不是 铅要多年以后才会分解
no.Lead wouldn't have started toabcdisintegrate till years after.
但可能会加重恐惧
But it could have exacerbated the fear.
我不想改变
I don't need to change.
你虽这么想
I know you think that.
但你的生活会变好
But your lifecould be better.
你可以选择
You--you--you'dhaveabcchoices.
他撒谎
He's lying.
撒什么慌?
About what?
每一件事 关于他的生活
About everything. About his life.
他在这儿根本不觉得快乐abc凄惨得很
He doesn't even think he'sabchappy here. He's miserable.
- 我什么都有abc- 是吗?
- I've got everythingI need.abc- Yeah?
为什么Taub在走廊发现玫瑰花瓣?
Well, then why did taub find roseabcpetals in your entry hallway?
我觉得有点古怪
Struck me as a little weird.
本以为和医学相关
Thought it might be medically relevant.
但却告诉我你是多么可怜
But it actually just toldabcme that you were pathetic.
你在门口昏倒那天
The day you crashed in your entry way...
是你女朋友的生日
was your girlfriend'sbirthday.
你不是去取信
You weren't there for the mail.
你是想去她的墓地放束鲜花
You were trying to golayabcflowers on her grave.
是的 他有创伤后应激障碍
Yeah, he's got ptsd.
是的 他也有陌生环境恐惧症
Yeah, he's agoraphobic.
他也是个懦夫
He's also a coward.
你想改变 就得行动
You want to changeabcyour life, do something.
别信自己编出的理由
Don't believe your own rationalizations.
别把自己关起来 假装很快乐
Don't lock yourselfabcup,pretend you're happy.
你是对的 我丈夫的事 影响了我
You were right. About myabchusband. It affected me.
现在还没能走出来
It still affects me.
你想说你永远不能--
If you're saying you'llabcnever be able to--
我理出一格空抽屉给你用
I cleaned out a drawer for you.
还挺大的
Like a big one.
* 我爱上个姑娘 *
* Im in love with a girl *
* 世上最好的姑娘 *
* Finest girl in the world *
* 我竟然会这样 *
* I didnt know I could feel this way *
* 日日思念着她 *
* Think about her all the time *
* 放她在心间 *
* Always on my mind *
* 我不懂得爱 *
* I didnt know about love *
* 为她千般都情愿 *
* All that a man should do is true *
* 千般都情愿 *
* 爱上一个姑娘 *
* Im in love with a girl *
* 世上最好的姑娘 *
* Finest girl in the world *
* 我竟然也会这样 *
* I didnt know this could happen to me *